

DAM LE KHANH LINH

SALES AND MARKETING/ CUSTOMER SERVICE

CONTACT

Tel: +84 936401302

Email: damle.khanhlinh2812@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/linh-dam2812 Address: Tan Phu District, HCMC

PERSONAL PROFILE

Α oriented fresh araduate majoring in Tourism and Hospitality field with experience in Event Planning, Marketing and Customer Service. work under pressure, learn fast and adapt quickly, cooperate well in team and individual work. Want to develop in sales and marketing in hospitality industry.

passionate and detail-

EDUCATION

RMIT Vietnam University Bachelor of Tourism and Hospitality Management

Relevant subjects: Event Management, International Food & Beverage Management, Room Division Management, Digital Marketing Communication, Consumer's Psychology, and Behavior Clubs: RMIT SGS Tourism & Hospitality Club, RMIT SGS Badminton Club, RMIT Hanoi RED Core Team.

REFERENCES

Kristy Marland - General Manager of Blue Ocean Resort Mui Ne

Tel: +84 - (0)252 - 3847 322 Email:

gm@blueoceanresort.com.vn

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blue Ocean Resort Mui Ne | NOV 2020 - JAN 2021 Customer Service Intern

- Interned in Reception, Reservations, Food & Beverage departments.

Responsibilities:

- Assisted in departments' daily tasks
- Supported in preparing, promoting, setting up, and running in-house events.
- Communicate with in-house guests to ask for their staying experience feedback.

Achievements: Successfully preparing promotional materials for resort events: Santa's Sunset Beach Food Festival, Christmas Eve. and New Year's Eve.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

RMIT SGS Tourism & Hospitality Management Club | FEB 2020 - OCT 2020

Event Planner

Responsibilities:

- Come up with new project ideas and event management.
- Develop standard templates for future projects to apply.
- Gather feedback from other departments to improve the working process.

Achievements: Participate in organizing and preparing for successful club events: Travel Taste challenge, Career Mentoring Week, Panel Discussion, and Hoteliers Race.

RMIT Event Drive (RED) Team (Hanoi Campus) | SEP 2018 - MAY 2019

Training Supervisor

Responsibilities:

- Supervise & Support Fitness Training Members.
- Track REC Members Data & Training Progress.
- Contribute ideas to implement & organize Fitness Activities and Support Student Life's Activities and Events.

Achievements:

- Silver Certificate for excellent volunteer contribution of RMIT Student Life Department 2017-2018
- Successfully organizing and supporting RMIT Hanoi Founder's Carnival, RMIT Graduation Day 2018, and RMIT R-Warrior Event.